Guide to the Felipe Ehrenberg Papers, ca. 1964-2000
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondencia
  - Subseries 1E: Printouts of Email, Documents, and Other Miscellaneous Material Contained on Zip Disk
    - Performas / Fotos fusco: indice.txt (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Performas / Muertos 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Performas: Miscellaneous digital images, text. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Periodismo / Alo-Com (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Periodismo / AlterEgo (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Periodismo / Antolog-Ing (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Periodismo / Artvance (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Periodismo / Astillero (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Periodismo / BonVivant (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Periodismo / Col-Virtual (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Periodismo / Curuare (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Periodismo / Finacerio / 97 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Periodismo / Finacerio / 98 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Periodismo / Finacerio: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Periodismo / Frontera (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Periodismo / In Site (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Periodismo / La Maquina (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Periodismo / Milenio (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / Libro (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Cartas (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Col-00 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Col-01 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Col-98 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Col-99 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista / NI-Ideas (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Periodismo / Nuevo Inversionista: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Periodismo / OpEd-MiedoDerecha (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Periodismo / Origina (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Periodismo / Ovaciones / 1999 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Periodismo / Ovaciones / 2000 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Periodismo / Ovaciones: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Periodismo / Rasgadodeboca (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Periodismo / Reforma (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Periodismo / SaberArte (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Periodismo: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Periodismo: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [2 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Polemicas / correo (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Polemicas: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Politica /Chop00 / Adhesiones (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Politica /Chop00 / Correo (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Politica /Chop00 / Correo2 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Politica /Chop00 / Medios (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Politica /Chop00: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Politica /Chop00: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. [2 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Ponencias (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Pres-Intros-Rec / Ensayos (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Pres-Intros-Rec / Presentaciones (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Pres-Intros-Rec / Recomendaciones (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Pres-Intros-Rec: Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Subastas (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Teoria [1 of 4] (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Teoria [2 of 4] (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Teoria [3 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Teoria [4 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous email, documents, etc. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Series 2. Criticos y Cronistas
  - Acha, Juan (Articulos Uno Mas Uno) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Acha, Juan (curriculum y correspondencia) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Ashton, Dore (EUA) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Barnitz, Jacqueline (EUA) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Bellinghausen, Hermann (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Blandford, Linda (EUA) (The Observer) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Blas Galindo, Carlos (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Brett, Guy (Ing.) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Briers, David (UK) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Comunicacion (Emmanuel Carballo) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Cockroft, Eva (EUA) (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Cordero, Karen (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Corlett, A. W. (Faculty of Art Design) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Criticos vs. Criticos (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Debroise, Oliver (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - De Ibarrola (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Del Conde, Teresa (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Dornbierer, Manu (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Eder, Rita (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Emerich, Luis Carlos (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Espinoza de los Monteros, Santiago (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Ferrer, Elizabeth (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Galindo, Blas (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Garcia Canclini, Nestor (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Garzon Cespedes, Francisco (OCLAE) [Organization Continental Latino Americana de Estudiantes] (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Glantz, Margo (Articulos uno mas uno) Genealogias (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gonzalez, Blanca (Universidad Ibero Americana) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Gonzalez Lobo, Carlos (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Gonzalez Quijano, Jose (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Gutierrez Vega, Hugo (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Haupt, Gerhard (Critico) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Haynes, Jim (Promotor) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Hernandez Campos, Jorge (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Hijar, Alberto (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Hoffberg, Judith (Umbrella) (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Joysmith, Toby (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Kapur, Geeta (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Korman, Mike (KPFA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Krantz, Claire (Copias Art, New Art Examiner, February ""85) (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Licuo, Dominique (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Mandoki, Katya (Articulos uno mas uno) (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Manrique, Jorge Alberto (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Merewether, Charles (Australia) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota Review (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Moctezuma Lopez, Juan (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Monsivais, Carlos (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Moyssen (Hijo), Javier (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Nava, Thelma (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Naylor, Colin (Editor, UK) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Neville, Richard (UK) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - New Art Examiner (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Nuncio, Abraham (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Olea, Oscar (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Pacello, Julio (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Piazza, Luis Guillermo (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Pommier, Claudine (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Provost, Giselle (France) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Ramirez, Mari Carmen (Puerto Rico) (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Retamar, Robert Fernandez (Cuba) (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rodriguez, Prampolini, Ida (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Roukes, N.M. (Calgary University) (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Schmilchuck, Graciela (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Silva, Ludovico (Caracas) (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Sorell, Victor (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Springer, Jose Manuel (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Stein, Judy (EUA) (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Tibol, Raquel - Articulos (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Tibol, Raquel - Correspondencia (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Torres, Michua (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Trujillo, M. Gabriel (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Vilchis, Martha (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Series 3: Varios Politica
  - Amnistia International (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Argentina: Desaparecidos politicos (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Artists Call (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Chiapas '94 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Chicago (communidad Hispanica) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Chicanos - politica - 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Chicanos - Tijuana, Mexicali, Calexico - Arte (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Chicanos Mission Cultural Center (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Chile (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Colombia Politica varios (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Congreso Reestructuracion ENAP, 1976 [Escuela Nacional de Artes Platicas] (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Costa Rica Politica (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Cuba (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Cuba, Va Por (92) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - CTACC [Corriente Trabajadores Arte Ciencia y la Cultura] (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Derechos de Autor (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - El Salvador (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Etiopa (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Foro nacional en defensa de la libertad de expresion e informacion popular (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Fronteras - Articulos, ensayos y varios (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Comision de la Verdad (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Guatemala (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Indigenismo - Bilinguismo (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Indigenismo - Rio Balsas - '90 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Indigenismo - Proyecto Linguistico Guggenheim (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Indigenismo - Pueblos Indios - O.N.G. Reunion '92 [Organizaciones No Gubernamentales ?] (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Indigenismo - Racismo (varios) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Indigenismo - Descubrimiento de America - V centario (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Juchitan (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Negritud, Africa / Brasil (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Nicaragua - politica [1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Nicaragua - politica [2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Pendientes (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Peru - politica (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Plebicito (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Politica Varios (copias articulos A. Riding) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - PRD - 1994 - Militancia (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - PRD Varios (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Premio Internacional Benito Juarez (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - PSUM - Candidatura Distrito 36 - 1982 [Partitio Socialista unificado de Mexico] (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico / Varios (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Tarjeta de Identidad (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - UPD [Union de Periodistas Democraticos] (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - U V Expulsion [Universidad Veracruzana] (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - U V y D 19 Sept. [Union de Vecinos y Damnificados] (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Varios (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Series 4: Beau Geste Press
  - Mayor (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Andersen, Eric (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Atkinson, Conrad (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Attalai, Gabor (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Barbossa, Diego (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Baschet, Francois (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Benson, Vale (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Bertoni, Claudio (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Black, Jeannie (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Bichnell, Lawrence (Albion Village Press) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Bley, Carla (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Blin, Claude (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Blitzinformation (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Boycott, Rosie (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Brake, Derek (Last Fly) (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Brena, Jorge (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Brown, Herb (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Brown, Paul (Trans Gravity) (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Brun, Adrian (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Buck, Paul (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Burga, Teresa (Concept. Peruvana) (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Canada Art Writers (Dave Zacow) (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Carraballo, Jorge (Uruguay) (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Carrega, Ugo (Centro Tool) (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Caruso, Luciano (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Caravalho, Antonio Claudio (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - CAYC [Centro de Arte Y Comunicacion] [1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - CAYC [Centro de Arte Y Comunicacion] [2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - CAYC [Centro de Arte Y Comunicacion] Hungria '74 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Challifour, G. (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Cook, Geoffrey (U.S.) (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Cordes, Chris (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Cortazar, Julio (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Corzas, Francisco y Bianca (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - COSMEP [Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers] BGP [Beau Geste Press] '75 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - COSMEP [Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers] BGP [Beau Geste Press] '74 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Costa, Tony (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Cozens, Andrew (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Crozier, Robin (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Culla, Daniel (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Cunliffe, Dave (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Dadaland (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - De Swaan, Silvia (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - DeVart, Guy - cineaste frances (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Dos Santos, Bartolomeu (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Echevarren, Roberto (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - El Corno Emplumado (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Ellis, Aidan (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - El-Rayess, Aref (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Erlij, Tania (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - E.S.P. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Export, Valie (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Felguerez, Manuel (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Fibich, Felix (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Finch, Peter (Editor) (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Finlayson, Logan (Holy Cow) (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Fisher, Alan (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Fluxus (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Foppa, Alaide - Desaparicion (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Fotos Varios: Beau Geste (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Friedfinnsson, Hreinn (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Friedman, Ken at Omen Press (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Galerie S:t petrie - Jean Sellem (BGP) [beau Geste Press] (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Gonzalez, Camarena Jorge (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Goodacre, G.J. (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Gordon, Maxwell (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Groh, Klaus (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Gudmundsson, Kristian (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Gurrola, Juan Jose (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Haut, Woody (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Hendricks, Marten (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Hernandez de Ossorno, Mariano (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Herscovitz, Marcia (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Hickman, Ken (U.K.) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hidalgo, Juan (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hodgkiss, Peter (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Huerta, Efrain (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Icaza, Francisco (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Illardo, Ronald (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Information Varias (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Jaso, Luis (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Jeffreys, Marc (TNT) (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Jimenez Luna, Gerardo (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Jordana, Elena (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Joris, Pierre (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Juarez, Heriberto (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Kaltenbeck, Franz (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Kamnitzer, Luis y Lilane Porter (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Kauffer, Raul (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Kearny, John (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Kedem, Moshe y Rimona (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Kelly, Bernard J. (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Kelly, Robert (U.K.) (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Kennedy, Peter (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Kepeneys, Pal (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Kerciu, Ray (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Klassnik, Robin (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Knigge, Peter (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Knowles, Alison (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Koiikee, Riyoo y Hiroko (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Kosugi, Takehisa (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Kriesche, Richard (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Landau, Jake (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Landau, Myra (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Legget, Michael (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lerner, Richard (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Leventhal, Peter and Irina (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Levin, Baron (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Levine, Steve and Patty (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Liggings, John (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Love Beast (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Maler, Leopoldo (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Marroquin, Raul (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Maurer, Dora (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Maya, Pepe (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - McCall, Anthony (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - McCallion, Barry (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, Ulli (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - de Medalla, David Cortes (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Miller, David (U.K.) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Miller, Roland (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Moore, Claire (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Mora, Phillipe (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Nakajima, Yoshio (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Nancarron, Conlin (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Nations, Opal L. [1] [contains The Man Who Entered Pictures, ts.] (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Nations, Opal L. [2] (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - New York Corres - Sponge Dance School of Vancouver (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Nez, David (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Nyman, Michael (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Orlando, Felipe (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Padilla, Heberto (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Parcerisas, Francesco (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Parra, Carmen (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Pellegrino, Alberto (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Pintado, Jose Manuel - T.V. y Galeria (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Planet Drum - Peter Berg (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Plant, John (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Poetry Plaza (Terry Woolfe) (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Powers, Kevin (State University of New York) (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Priani, Ernesto (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Riedel, Fritz (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Rius, Eduardo (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Rehfeldt, Roberto (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Reynolds, Tim (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Ian (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Robinson, John (Joe Dimaggio Press) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Rocha, Ricardo (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - de Rook, G.J. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome (Geronimo) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Rothon, Tony (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Saito, Takako (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Salt Lick Press (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Sawyer, David (Musico, U.K.) (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Schmuck America Latina (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Schneeman, Carolee (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Sigi Krauss Gallery (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Siqueros [David Alfaro] (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Trabajos Publicitarios, U.K. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Trigram Press Limited (Asa Benveniste) (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Smith Pauline, U.K. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Stake, Chuck (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Studio Brescia (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Sugarman, George (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Summers, Rod (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Tajiri, Shinkichi (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Tamayo, [Rufini] (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Telling, Derek (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - The Other Cinema (Nick Hart Williams) (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Tilson, Joe (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Todorovic, Miroljub (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Urban, Janos (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Vautier, Ben (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Vehicule Art (Montreal) Inc. (Suzy Lake) (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Vicuna, Cecilia (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Paris Agreement (BGP) [Beau Geste Press] (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Von Frakenberg, Gisela (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Ward, Tony (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Weibel, Peter (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Wenzel, Marian (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Wesley, John (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Wewerka, Stefan (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Heathcote (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Woodrow, Paul and Judy (Works) (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Werz, Herve (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Zetterling, Mai (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Zoline, Pamela (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Zui (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Zuniga, Pepe (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Breakwell, Ian (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Comunas (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Varios - Beau Geste Press (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Welch, Chris and Mad [Madeline] (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Haltos 2 Ornos
  - Programcion de eventos: Actas constitutivas (copias) mimeocursos (SEP) CREN - SEP, [Centro Regional de Educacion Normal - Secretaria de Educacion Publica] Iguala '82 - '83 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Haltos 2 Ornos, Felipe Ehrenberg: Correspondencia y documentos varios - SEP [Secretaria de Educacion Publica] (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Haltos 2 Ornos, Felipe Ehrenberg: Correspondencia, documentos, memorandums; varios - ISSSTE (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - En todo Mexico las artes plasticas (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Fotos Labor Editorial H2O (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - H2O ISSSTE - Depto Artes Plasticas Propsiciones (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - H2O Programas Estalas (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - H2O - ISSSTE - Programa Manual Mural Para ""El dia"" (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - H2O - ISSSTE - Artes Plasticas Varios (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - H2O - ISSSTE - Susana Alexander - Creatividad en la Educacion (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - H2O - ISSSTE - Prensa (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Juegos, Fotocopias, Formas, Horarios (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - La Higiene Tambien es Cultura (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Mimeo, Photos Revelar y Archivar (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Mimeo, Produciones / DIversos [1 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Mimeo, Produciones / DIversos [2 of 2] (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Haltos 2 Ornos Prensa (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Haltos 2 0rnos - Programas Syllabus / Labor Editorial / Mural y Cartel (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - H2O - SEP [Haltos 2 Ornos - Secretaria de Educacion Publica] / Direccion General de Promocion Cultural - Hecelchakan / Labor editorial mural (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - H2O - SEP [Haltos 2 Ornos - Secretaria de Educacion Publica] / Depto. Artes Plasticas Proposiciones (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Bueno, Alicia Haltos 2 Ornos (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Carey, Caty (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Cervantes, Graciela (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Checci, Anna (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - DeJesus Salazar, Nicholas (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - del Campo, Ana Cecelia (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Duran Cerrato, Ruben (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Ehrenberg, Felipe (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Escalante, Alejandro (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Esparza, Radaid (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Galvan, Jesus (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Guzman, Jose Jesus (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Guzman, Edgar (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Hernandwz Guzman, Carlos (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Kamffer, Cuauhemoc (Curriculum and Reporte) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Kolteniuk, Bertha (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Limenes, Marcos (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Molino, Ernesto (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Montaner, Eliana (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Navarro, Alejandro (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Paz Salinas, Raul (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Perez Grovas, Rafael (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Rebelledo, Santiago (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Reyes Cordereo, Jesus (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Rodriguez, Sofia (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Rotondo, Maribel (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Sepulveda, Roberto (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Torres, Jorge (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Varios: Arriaga, Flor; Galvan, Martin; Hernandez, Luciano; Ortega, Malu; Taboada, Liliana (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Directorio Instructores Labor Editorial - Cartel - Pintura - mural - Mimeografia (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Series 6: Labor Periodistica
  - Azteca T.V. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Berger, John: 4 Ensayos Traduccion (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Cuestion: Articulos publicados 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Cuestion: MMSS de Enero a Junio de 1981 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Cuestion: Articulos Pendientes (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Revista Comunicacion - Hojas Originales (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Cultures in Contention (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Diario Oposicion (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - El Economista (Refranero Ehrenberg) (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - El Finaciero (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - El Finaciero - Columna Knosos (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - El Finaciero - Columna ojo Avisor (Articulos Publicados) (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - El Gallo Ilustrado (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - El Gallo Ilustrado (replica ""El Muralismo Vive"") (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Filo Rojo (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - La Garrapata (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Para Gente Grande - I Televisa (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Gente Grande II (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Ibero Texto Galerias 1991 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Latin American Art - Ensayo - F.E. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Leonardo E.U.A. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Notomex ""96 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Novedades MMSS Ene / Jun 1990 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Nuestro Siglo (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Ovaciones Articulos Ineditos Perdientes (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Ovaciones Copias de Articulos Seleccionados (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Ovaciones - Archivo (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Ovaciones - Concurso Columnas (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ovaciones - Impresos y Copias 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ovaciones - Impresos y Copias 1980 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Ovaciones - Impresos y Copias 1979 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Ovaciones - Impresos y Copias 1978 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Ovaciones MMSS Enero a Junio de 1981 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Ovaciones MMSS Julio a Diciembre de 1981 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Ovaciones MMSS - Enero a Junio de 1980 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Ovaciones MMSS - de Julio a Diciembre 1980 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Ovaciones MMSS de Enero a Junio 1979 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Ovaciones MMSS de Julio a Diciembre1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Ovaciones MMSS 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Ovaciones - Articulos Rechazados (Censura o Extemporaneos) (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - de Par en Par (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - El Regional - Columna (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - PM - LA: (Art Space y Uno mas Uno) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Plural - Murales (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Revista Punto: MMSS (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Revista Punto: Impresos y Copias (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - El Sol de Mexico (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - El Sol de Mexico: Articulos Publicados y renuncia (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Sucesos - Jedorowski (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Temas Posibles Articulos (Caduco) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Uno mas Uno (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - El Universal (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Vallarta: Noticias del Puerto (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Vertigo: Revista Modas y Cultura (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Vidrios Rotos Promo '96 (Box 58, Folder 8)